Hello hi friends my name is Deepak Jain
and I am the founder of Infinity Games Alleppey
friends if you are thinking of purchasing health insurance for your family then the
most difficult task for you is to decide
which plan of which company you should select some
company gives you room rent capping some
company gives disease capping
some company charges payment so
after looking at all these things we feel
that among all these selecting the top line
for your family is a very
difficult task so friends let's simplify
this entire task for you guys
today you
can see on your screen MP3 health plans for u
so friends recently live mitne bakshekh
dot org conducted a
survey and gave a rating to the insurance companies i.e.
health insurance products
and in that rating please share with you the top 15 health
insurance plans which are currently available in India so
friends today in this ranking  Let's
try to understand this. First of all,
before coming to these rankings, let us tell you some basic
understanding of how this ranking has been
decided. So
first of all, this ranking has been decided
on two plus one basis, that is, husband,
wife and one child and according to Mumbai,
in the premium league, leaving close to Rs 10 lakh, next, the
entry
taken in this is 65, that is, this selection has been given only
for those members who are less than six inches tall.
So let us talk about, here you people have been
given product rating,
what benefits do you get in the product,
next, what you will get in this is the
track record
of the company, in what type of
column you will see the overall rating,
how many stars the company got and now this
rating has been given, it is given from the top five stars.
If you see in the photo, here
you can see that the
premium of Jhal products is
on the higher side. Here, if you see the rating less,
then the premium  You will find it on the lower side, so first of all
we talk about
Nimbu Pa Health Reward Shoaib, Nibha's
product is Health Reward Shoaib, its
product rating is 4.5,
so the track record rating is
3.7, the overall rating of this product is 4.7
stars, and the premium affordability
rating is 3. Next now let's talk about Royal
Sundaram's Lifeline Supreme plan, its
product rating is four points, the
claim track record rating is 3.8, the overall
rating is 4.5, the premium photo gallery
rating is 2.5, the
third position is occupied by Nimbu Pa, many health
companies, Planets, its pro point is
located, the claim track record rating is
3.7, the overall rating is 4.5 stars, the premium
quality rating of this plan is
on the eighth position, Magma HD's One Help
Premium plan, its product rating is
4.6, so the track record is 4.5, the overall
rating of this product is 4.5 and the premium
activity rating is 4. Next now let's talk about
HDFC Ergo's Optima
Restore
product rating, pain track record
1.58, overall rating 4.3, length premium  A
probability rating respect in the next goes to
Aditya Birla Help's Active
Health Platinum Premier Plan product
rating is 4 points Please recording
13.9 overall rating this point 3 star
premium quality rating this five
edelweiss general Tata Family Health
Insurance Gold Plan product rating
this points and claim track recording this
three points 72 rating this point 3
premium quality rating a3 point five
Next comes Clear Insurance's Care's
new spare product rating that now let's talk about so
4.3 claim track recording this
ignorant 4.3 overall rating points three and
premium probability rating of this
product is
30 ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Company's product is Complete Health
Insurance Health LED Plan product
rating is 4.2 claim track recording this
point 7 overall rating this point three
premium probability rating this
next now let's talk about HDFC Ergo
's Optimus Secure so product rating is
4.9 claim track recording this 1.5
overall rating this point two and premium
quality return gift for next now  Let's talk about
two digit health insurance
Comfort Problem product rating of this plan is
for co lute plain track record
3.3 low overall rating this point to
premium activity rating A3
symptoms let's talk about Money Pal Signal's
Profile Plus plan
product rating it has a three layer track
record rating of
3.9 overall rating this point to premium A
possibility rating 3.5
Chola MS Flexis Health product
rating of this plan is 4.1 claim track
record
operating 4.7 overall rating this point to
premium Fertility Rate English 2.5
comes at protein position Aditya Birla
Health's Active Ashva product rating this
point to claim track record rating is
3.9 overall rating this point One Free that
I possibility rating list 2.5 in and
Star Health's
Complaint Helpline product is at fine position but this
plan has 4.2 love track record
rating 3.5 overall rating this point Vansdhar
and premium affordability rating is 3.5
in so friends if you are looking for
a health plan for your family  If you are looking to buy a good health insurance
policy, then Live
Mit has made this task very easy for you and
you can purchase a plan for your family by selecting from these top-15 plans.
If you
want to know the complete details of these products, then
we have already shared detailed videos of some of these products
on our channel.
We are sharing the links of the plans which we have already
shared in the description with you people and still
if you feel that you have any preference related to any
health insurance plan, then
please coordinate with our team on the number written on the description.
So friends, thank you, thank you so much
for watching the video. Thank you too.